Dipta Das

(C) 347-322-3057 | diptadas29@yahoo.com | Staten Island, NY 10304

SUMMARY

4+ years of Coding in Java, Python, and Web Optimization. Focused and driven to learn more and improve. Self-created mobile apps and websites, with experience in UX/UI design as well as photoshop skills. Also, enjoy creating GBA games, sports, volunteering in soup kitchens, and photography.

SKILLS

- Python
- Javascript (React)
- HTML/CSS
- Java
- Excel

- SQL
- UI/UX
- Bilingual in Bengali
- Mobile application development
- Swift

EXPERIENCE

Web Development (intern/temp), Albany Law, January 2019-May 2019 Albany, New York

- Front Fnd.
- Help fix buas.
- Responsible for using and editing Javascript and PHP.
- Build out your forms entirely
 - One for lobbying expenses
 - One for lobbying activities
 - One for retrieving data from the lobbying/expenses database
- Add content from Albany Law
- Build the navigation/footer
- Add additional content as you see fit to describe your forms
- Attach wireframes/write ups to explain things you weren't able to get working

Mobile Application (intern), SUNY Albany, August 2020-December 2020 Albany, New York

- Designed, developed, tested prototype of mobile application using Python (Tkinter).
- Helped with web design using HTML, CSS, Javascript.
- Develop design features using Photoshop.
- Edited the App interface and output.
- Help fix bugs.

Robotics/Packages Department, Amazon., March 2019-August 2019 Staten Island, New York

- Responsible for Packaging.
- Helping robotic departments.

Recovery, BJ's Wholesale Club Inc., January 2020-March 2020 (Covid) Albany, New York

- Provided assistance with purchases, locating items, and signing up for rewards programs.
- Helped customers find specific products, answering questions, and offering advice.
- Notified security of suspected theft, including descriptions of individuals and items stolen to help control store losses.
- Completed daily recovery tasks to keep areas clean and neat for maximum efficiency.
- Welcomed customers, offering assistance to help find necessary store items.
- Assisted customers with account updates, new service additions, and promotional offers.
- Inspected items for damage and reported issues to the supervisor to return unsalable merchandise and obtain replacements for customers.
- Organized storage of articles in bins, floors, shelves, and assigned areas according to product categories.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

High School Diploma

Susan E Wagner High School, Staten Island NY 2017

- Honor Roll Sophomore, Junior, Senior year.
- Law Academy
- Council of Unity Member (Also award)
- Key Club Member

Bachelor of Science

Information of Technology - Software Development, SUNY At Albany, Albany NY Expected in 2021

• Minor in Computer Science

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Honor Rolls in High School
- Council for Unity Leadership Award
- Academy of Law and Politics